aurlay.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Online Shopping in Pakistan - Buy, Sell online

We are highly great full to you for your joining on aurlay.com managed by MARS INTERNATIONAL. We always respect our customers’ privacy that’s why we protect their personal information. For more information, please read this Privacy & Secrecy Policy. This Privacy & Secrecy Policy will explain the steps of security; we take, to protect your personal information. This Privacy & Secrecy Policy will also tell how we collect, use and reveal your personal information (under certain conditions). Your visiting to this Site directly or indirectly, automatically will consider your acceptance to this Policy. We only use your name and other related information if it needed or if it is necessary for dealings with you. We will take information only, either it is required by law or it is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. You can also visit and browse this Site without providing any personal details/

### Data We Collect

When you place an order then we need to collect various pieces of information according to your order. We process on provided data for home delivery, for services and for any possible later claims. We may collect personal information including, which could be, your title, name, gender, date of birth, email address, postal address, delivery address as well as telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details.

Furthermore, this information will be used to manage your account; for verification and carrying out financial transactions for payment; audit the downloaded data from our website etc. we may contact you via email with your permission & will provide you details of other products and services. If you don’t want to receive any marketing communications from us, you can unsubscribe our marketing promotional emails at any time.

We may pass your name and address to a third party for home delivery of the product (for example to our courier or supplier).

Payments must be processed by our agent or as we provided you information. You must follow that process in order to get your order at home. Your actual order details are stored with us but for security purpose we cannot retrieve that directly. However, you could access that information by logging into your account on the website. In your account you can view the details of your orders, those have been completed, those that are open and those that are shortly to be dispatched and manage your address details, bank details and any newsletter on which you may have subscribed. Your data is your personal entity & identity so, please do not share with any one especially to unknown, unauthorized third party & should keep it confidential. We are not responsible for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

### Your Personal Information Usage

Your personal information could be used for opinion and market research. Those details will be used without nominating you and only for statistical purposes. You can ask us not to use that information at any time. Your participation in surveys or opinion polls and your answers to that surveys or opinion polls will not be given to third parties. Forwarding of your email address is only necessary when you take part in competition. We save those answers of surveys or opinion polls separately from your email address.

We may also send you other information regarding about us, our other websites, products, sales promotions, and newsletters, anything relating to companies in our group or our business partners. If you don’t want to receive any of these additional information then please click the ‘unsubscribe’. Within 7 working days (excluding Saturday, Sunday, & public holidays anywhere in Pakistan) of receiving of this request we will stop to send information, as you requested. If your request is unclear then we will contact you for clarification.

We may further use data to find out your general location, and supply that data to third parties such as publishers. However, this data will be used only for other purpose & that data will not be capable of identifying you personally.

### Cookies:

The approval of cookies is not necessary for visiting this Site. However we want to make it clear that the function of “basket” is on the Site is only available and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. Cookies are small text files which distinguish your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit the certain pages of our website. This information is stored via your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used to identify your Internet Protocol (IP) address. In order to save your time when you visit our Site, or want to enter the Site, we only use cookies for your ease. Via cookies, we remember who you are, when you modified your shopping cart without re-entering your email address. It is not used for gathering or using any other information about you as for targeted advertising etc. You can set your browser not accept cookies, but after this setting your Site use could be restricted. Please accept our guarantee that we don’t use cookies for personal or private details and it’s free from viruses. If you want to go for further details about cookies then please visit to https://www.allaboutcookies.org or details about its removal from your browser then visit to https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.

This website also uses Google Analytics which analysis the web services, provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies. To help the website analyze that how users use the website, cookie tells about your use of the website including your IP address which is passed on and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google use this information for evaluation of your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and other services about website activity and use of internet. If there is need by law to transfer this information to third party, then Google may also transfer. On Google’s behalf, third parties process the information. Google will not share your IP address with any other data held by Google. You could reject the use of cookies via your browser setting. However please note that you may not be able to use the full functions of this website if you do so. By using this website, you show that you are agree with the processing of data by Google for the purposes set out above.

### Your Rights

You have the right to request the access to your personal data on which we process. You have the right to demand for the correction of any mistake in your data free of charge. At any stage you also have the right to stop us & ask us not to use your personal data for direct marketing purposes. For further support you can visit to our head office at “aurlay.com, Shahina Bad Backside of Heritage College, Gujranwala”.

### General

We can change or make amendments in this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site.
